const carsQuestions = [
    {
        question: " What is the best-selling car of all time?",
        correct_answer: "Toyota Corolla",
        incorrect_answers: ["Bolero", "Thar", "Rolls Royals"]
    },
    {
        question: "What does ABS stand for in the context of cars?",
        correct_answer: "Anti-lock Braking System",
        incorrect_answers: ["Automatic Brake System", "Advanced Brake Security", " Auto Brake Suppression"]
    },

    {
        question: " In a car engine, what does RPM stand for?",
        correct_answer: " Revolutions Per Minute",
        incorrect_answers: ["Revolutions Per Mile", " Regulated Power Mechanism", " Radial Performance Module"]
    },

    {
        question: "What does SUV stand for?",
        correct_answer: "Sports Utility Vehicle",
        incorrect_answers: ["Speedy Undercarriage Vehicle", "Super Urban Van", " Sport Utility Van"]
    },

    {
        question: "Which car company produces the Mustang model?",
        correct_answer: "Ford",
        incorrect_answers: ["Chevrolet", "Honda", " Toyota"]
    },

    {
        question: " What is the purpose of a catalytic converter in a car?",
        correct_answer: " Reduce Emissions",
        incorrect_answers: ["Enhance Engine Sound", "Improve Horsepower", "  Increase Fuel Efficiency"]
    },

    {
        question: " Which car company uses the slogan 'The Ultimate Driving Machine'? ",
        correct_answer: "BMW",
        incorrect_answers: ["Mercedes-Benz", "Audi", " Lexus"]
    },

    {
        question: "What does MPG stand for in the context of car fuel efficiency?",
        correct_answer: "Miles Per Gallon",
        incorrect_answers: ["Maximum Power Generation", "Advanced Brake Security", " Auto Brake Suppression"]
    },

    {
        question: "What does ABS stand for in the context of cars?",
        correct_answer: "Anti-lock Braking System",
        incorrect_answers: ["Automatic Brake System", "Advanced Brake Security", " Mileage Preservation Gauge"]
    },

    {
        question: " In car terms, what does the acronym HVAC stand for?",
        correct_answer: "Heating, Ventilation, and Air Conditioning",
        incorrect_answers: ["High Velocity Air Control", " Hydraulic Vehicle Air Control", "Heat, Vapor, and Air Conditioning"]
    },

    {
        question: "What is the purpose of the alternator in a car? ",
        correct_answer: "Generate Electricity",
        incorrect_answers: [" Control Engine Temperature", " Adjust Suspension", "Regulate Fuel Injection"]
    },

    {
        question: " Which country is known for producing the brand Toyota?",
        correct_answer: "Japan",
        incorrect_answers: ["Germany", " United States ", "South Korea"]
    },


    {
        question: " Which car company uses the slogan 'The Power of Dreams'? ",
        correct_answer: "Honda",
        incorrect_answers: ["Toyota", "Ford ", "Chevrolet"]
    },


    {
        question: "What is the purpose of the transmission in a car? ",
        correct_answer: "Transmit Power to Wheels",
        incorrect_answers: ["Control Steering", " Manage Brake System", "Regulate Fuel Injection"]
    
    },


    {
        question: "  What does EV stand for in the context of cars?",
        correct_answer: " Electric Vehicle",
        incorrect_answers: ["Engine Vehicle", " Efficient Van ", "Eco-friendly Vehicle"]
    },

    {
        question: "Which automaker produces the Mustang model?",
        correct_answer: "Ford",
        incorrect_answers: ["Chevrolet", "Dodge", "Toyota"]
    },
    {
        question: "What does the term 'horsepower' in car engines refer to?",
        correct_answer: "Power or energy produced by the engine",
        incorrect_answers: ["Top speed of the car", "Fuel efficiency", "Weight of the car"]
    },
    {
        question: "In what country did the famous luxury car manufacturer Ferrari originate?",
        correct_answer: "Italy",
        incorrect_answers: ["Germany", "France", "United States"]
    },
    {
        question: "Which hybrid car model is known for its fuel efficiency and environmental friendliness?",
        correct_answer: "Toyota Prius",
        incorrect_answers: ["Chevrolet Volt", "Honda Accord Hybrid", "Ford Fusion Hybrid"]
    },
    {
        question: "What is the top speed of the Bugatti Chiron, one of the fastest production cars?",
        correct_answer: "261 mph (420 km/h)",
        incorrect_answers: ["220 mph (354 km/h)", "280 mph (450 km/h)", "300 mph (483 km/h)"]
    },







];